[{"answer": "Thats right", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Its very good, indeed", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Whats weird about that", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Guess Im not like most women", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Good. Thats an honest answer. And why dont you like coming here", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Is it just my cheery personality that makes your skin itch", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " So, what did you do", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Molested little girls", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Fucking Tigers. They got no pitching except for a bunch of green kids straight out of Double A or Southern Cal.  How was the party", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "The birthday party", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "How do you feel about that", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You have no feelings for your niece", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I dont feel anything", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "She was born after they put me away. How can I have feelings", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "She was born after they put me away. How can I have feelings", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Have to talk about something", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Do you think youre crazy", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Why do you think youre here", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Will I ever be normal", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You couldnt say", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "How do they know", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " What is your idea of being a Jew", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What is your idea of being normal", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Whatever my ideas are of being a Jew is not going to help you.  Why dont we continue this on Thursday", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Fuck you, my friend", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You dont know", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I know", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I know youre frustrated, my friend, but", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " Is it their innocence? Their beauty?..", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "They seduce you", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Are you serious", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Not ever", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " my friend, well pick up here next time", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Well talk about it more on Thursday", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Im not scared", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Maybe you should be", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " When did it all start", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "If by", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I dont know", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Thats my answer", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Im relaxed", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Nothing. Can I open my eyes", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I dont see", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "In my bed too", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Were little kids", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " When the two of you held each other. When you were ten or eleven and she was eight or nine. When your parents were out and the two of you were alone... completely alone in that big house", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "All right. A small house... with small rooms", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Im not a monster", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Maybe Im not a good man. Maybe inside Im bad, and Ill always be bad", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Sneak up behind me like that", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Whys it always my fucking problem", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "A solitary vireo. I like that one", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "How does it sound", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Sure you do. He cuts open the wolfs stomach, and the girl steps out alive", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Thats it. Little Red Riding Hood jumps out of the wolfs guts with hardly a scratch.  Ever see a seve", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": " Dont you have friends", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "A pretty girl like you should have a lot of friends", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Your daddy will always love you", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I know because... its just something I know", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " Time", "docId": "thewoodsman.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "I feel... okay", "qsentId": 62}]